The Kingdom at my screen There is a big recluse
I can't figure it out I think I'm at a loss
But when I've done it out You won't believe the fix
Turns out my package was a few single days dispersion
But now I'm coming out I'm running the pre-commit
Getting fast and getting longer than I'll admit
I checked in thoroughly Checking all the syntax
Now I have to push my core open Then I won't have to
Hack it up! Hack it up!
Now you face the workflow of the death I've got to push my changes to the branch
See how the actions gonna act I've been said Hack it up now!
I just want the change to be deployed The runner's making my blood wanna boil
But since I missed my starter flash I've gotta hack it up now!
Check out repo set up package Hack it up!
Build for man in the deep testing Hack it up!
We'll patch the docs and change the version Hack it up!
Merge the changes, start deploying Hack it up!
The change has been with him, workflow scheduled for 9
My whole plan to do a flow will fire up on time
After a few more hours I check on it again
Turns out my time zone isn't set to my love
So now, well never mind I'm gonna add open load dispatch
So I can test it though it feels like an escape hatch
But most it's gone, it's gone, I'll take it back
It seems but a powerful request that's gonna yell at me
Hack it up! Hack it up!
Now, to face the workflow of the depth I've gotta push my changes to the branch
See how the actions gonna act I've been said Hack it up now!
I just want the change to be deployed The runner's making my blood wanna boil
But since I missed my style of flash I've gotta
Hack it up now! Check out read full set of package
Hack it up! Build for man in the deep testing Hack it up!
We'll patch the docs and change the version Hack it up!
Merge the changes, start deploying Hack it up!
Hack it up! Hack it up!
Now, to face the workflow of the depth I've gotta push my changes to the branch
See how the actions gonna act I've been said Hack it up now!
I just want the change to be deployed The runner's making my blood wanna boil
But since I missed my style of flash I've gotta
Hack it up now! Check out read full set of package
Hack it up! Build for man in the deep testing Hack it up!
We'll patch the docs and change the version Hack it up!
Merge the changes, start deploying Hack it up!