I've been seen, I'm here to help you at your command You can install me right in
Here in the system or here in the project space Say my name and I'll assist
I can take care of the tasks of monotony Run those miscripts all at once
I hope that you feel a boost in efficiency I'll do this while you have fun
Alexin Line brings it full right to your console Alexin Line runs tests for you in the background
Alexin Line help me at hand when you say Alexin Line is on command
I'll bring you templates to help you mow down a plant Document all of your work
I'll help you calculate what the next version from here will be
Make them aware what will work I can help you to prepare before you commit
What checks are on is your choice When you are ready to show the world what you've done
What checks are on is your choice When you are ready to be
Alexin Line brings it full right to your console Alexin Line runs tests for you in the background
Alexin Line help me at hand when you say Alexin Line is on command
Bring the files, I'll write you out a plan Change the version, your raft will be out in time
If you need my help, just run the command here in your terminal Install Alexin Line
Alexin Line brings it full right to your console Alexin Line runs tests for you in the background
Alexin Line help me at hand when you say Alexin Line is on command