I think you're ready to push and show I've found problems you'd better know
People think that I'm too picky But I just got the gates of quality
Soar those objects, check that spelling I just wanna get you to your best
Missing symbol, check that spacing Put your work to the test
I'm checking, I'm checking Checking for no missed out things
I'm checking, I'm checking Making sure your work's all in order
I'm checking, I'm checking You sure this is your best work?
I'm conscious to discuss, I care And I have standards, you'd better have some too
Now we've got to define some rules You can think and I'll check for you
Even if they aren't what I use Make sure you follow them the whole way through
Set your standards, figure out your style Choose the rules that will help get your best
Be consistent, I'll still check it Put your work to the test
I'm checking, I'm checking Checking for no missed out things
I'm checking, I'm checking Making sure your work's all in order
I'm checking, I'm checking You sure this is your best work?
I just do this cause I care That you have standards and I will follow them
I'm checking, I'm checking Checking for no missed out things
I'm checking, I'm checking Making sure your work's all in order
I'm checking, I'm checking You sure this is your best work?
I just do this cause I care That you have standards and I will follow them too
Go commit yourself through the stage
Set your standards and you'll do great One more check and you'll be on your way
I'm checking, I'm checking Checking for no missed out things
I'm checking, I'm checking Making sure your work's all in order
I'm checking, I'm checking You sure this is your best work?
I just do this cause I care That you have standards and I will follow them
I'm checking, I'm checking Checking for no missed out things
I'm checking, I'm checking Making sure your work's all in order
I'm checking, I'm checking You sure this is your best work?
I just do this cause I care That you have standards and I will follow them too
I have standards, you better have some too