I know you've been checking me out, shall we take it to the next level now?
Cause I really wanna be there all for you, all for you
Come on now let's make a fresh start, pin my number then you can take me out
Can you see I really do care about you, about you
Although our calendars are imperfect at best
I'd like to organize time with you, with you
Just tell me when and I'll make it clear, all clear for you, all clear for you
I wanna be of utility, I'll help you on the run
I'll be the one here in the back while you go have some fun
Looking out for you tonight, I'll be the one you can rely on
Watch you go and watch me pass by, I'll be here, I'll commit to you
Though sometimes it won't be easy, you'll be here to bring out the best in me
And I'll hold myself to high standards for you, all for you
We'll grow as a pair, you and me
We'll build up a healthy dependency
You can build with me and I'll develop with you, I'm with you
I'll be with you when you're up or you're down
We'll deal with all our problems together, together
Just tell me what you want, I'll make it clear, all clear for you, all clear for you
One, three, one, go!
I wanna be of utility, I'll help you on the run
I'll be the one here in the back while you go have some fun
Looking out for you tonight, I'll be the one you can rely on
Watch you go and watch me pass by, I'll be here, I'll commit to you
Looking into our stack, I'll commit to you
We've got a lot to unpack, I'll commit to you
The environment that we're in, I'll commit to you
Delicate as a string, I'll commit to you
But I think you're my type, I'll commit to you
Oh, this feels all so right, I'll commit to you
Nothing stopping us now, I'll commit to you
Let's show them what we're all about
Two, three, four, go!
I wanna be of utility, I'll help you on the run
I'll commit to you
I'll be the one here in the back while you go have some fun
Looking out for you tonight, I'll be the one you can rely on
Watch you go and watch me pass by, I'll be here, I'll commit to you
I wanna be of utility, I'll help you on the run
I'll commit to you
I'll be the one here in the back while you go have some fun
Looking out for you tonight, I'll be the one you can rely on
Watch you go and watch me pass by, I'll be here, I'll commit to you
I'll commit to you